Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Standing committees, 1965-1986; MS2009 Series 13; 16.5 Linear feet
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13205- James Properties General Partnership Property, 4th St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13221- Nathanson Property, 122 10th St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13227- 608 Massachusetts Ave NE, 1980 April 15; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13232- Reich Property, 650 Independence Ave SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13237- 520 E St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13242- Roth Property, 401 10th St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13245- 212 F St. NE, 1980 May 20; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 30)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13247- Waldorf Property, 722 E St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 31)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13253- Ruskin Property, 921 North Carolina Ave SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 32)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13254- Shaw Property, 413 2nd St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 33)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13255- Kelly Property, 729 8th St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 34)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13257- Jacobs Property, 118 F St. NE, Undated; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 35)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13262- Halbert Blue Property, 1001 F St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 36)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13265- Eckhardt Property, 122 3rd St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 37)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13291- H.E. Goings Property, 711 G St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 38)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13296- Episcopal Diocese of Washington Property, 1340 Massachusetts Ave SE, 1976, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 39)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13300- Weinstein and Capen Property, 810 A St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 40)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13303- Gailor Property, 218-220 D St. SE, 1980-1981; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 41)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13311- Bevec Property, D St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 42)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13330- 1231 Potomac Ave SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 43)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13332- Houston and Padgen Property, 545 4th St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 44)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13359- Williams Property, 629 7th St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 45)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13341- Juhas Property, 1217 Massachusetts Ave SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 46)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13356- Nelson Property, 418 D St. SE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 47)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13053 and 13363- Canal and Ivy Associates Property, 55 Ivy St. SE, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13378- Quillian Property, Pennsylvania Ave SE and 6th St. SE, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13390- 629 Constitution Ave NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13400- Yon Toy Moy Property, 538 3rd St. NE, 1979-1980; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13405-13419, 1980-1981; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13420-13461, 1980-1981; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13462-13498, 1981; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13544-13609, 1981; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13619-13737, 1981-1982; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13738-13787, 1982; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13787-13840, 1982; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13847-13870, 1982; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13880-13996, 1982-1983; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14012-14032, 1983; Series 13 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14033-14097, 1983-1984; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14107-14115, 1984; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14116-14151, 1983-1984; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14155-14167, 1983-1984; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14187-14244, 1984-1985; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14246-14310, 1984-1985; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14315-14404, 1985; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14415-14572, 1986-1987; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14573-14707, 1987-1988; Series 13 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14712- Mount Jezreel Baptist Church Property, 510 E St. SE, 1987; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14719- W.H. Associates Property, 118 12th St. NE, 1987 - 1988; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14724- Kreiss Property, 623 A St. SE, 1987-1988; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14738-14759, 1987-1988; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14771-14805, 1988; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14809-14897, 1988; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14906-14946, 1988-1989; Series 13 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14938- Shell Oil Company Property, 1550 Pennsylvania Ave SE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14950- Morgan and Grove Property, 216 10th St. SE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14974- Dunphy Properties Inc. Property, 719 F St. NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14976- American Osteopathic Association Property, 300-302 F St. NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14977- 1318 Maryland Ave. NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14981- Eastern Market Associates Property, 228 7th St. SE, 1988; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14983- Terrafranca Property, Number 8 Barney Circle SE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14988- Hurle Property, 212 9th St. SE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 14990- J.C. Associates Property, 611 Pennsylvania Ave SE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15061- Potomac Development Corporation Property, 515 Capitol Court NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15065- Lowe Property, 619 Massachusetts Ave NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15066- 703 Maryland Ave NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15072- BBB Investment Inc. Property, 1101 C St. NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15075- 501 3rd St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15085- Bagan Jr. Property, 401 10th St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15086- Williams Property, 1531 A St. NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15095- Nelson Property, 434 13th St. NE, 1988 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15104- Reed and Kaupp Property, 313 9th St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15110- Watkins Property, 257 and 267 Warren St. NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15118- Ballenger Property, 450 New Jersey Ave SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15271- Corson Property, 506 3rd St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15123- O'Donnell and Oehler Property, 1359 Massachusetts Ave SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15131- Quillian Property, 603-605 Pennsylvania Ave SE and 318-326 6th St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15135- Smiley Property, 633 East Capitol St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15137- Gutman Property, 1220 North Carolina Ave NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15140- Wharton Property, 607 3rd St. NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15155- Hofen Property, 507 2nd St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15158- Mellen Property, 1237 and 1237 1/2 Duncan Pl NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15171- Peros Property, 320 D St. NE, 1987 - 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15188- Tiches Property, 501 East Capitol St. SE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15204 and 15205- Potomac Electric Power Company Property, 3400 Benning Rd. NE, 1989; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15220- Gurney and Kearney Property, D and 4th Streets SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15236- Huntley Property, 729 10th St. NE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15241- 826-828 10th St. NE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15248- Evans Property, 610 A St. SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15252- Quillian Property, 613 Pennsylvania Ave SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15256- Wilson and Harris Property, 1213 Walter St. SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15261- Washington Community Fellowship Property, 907 Maryland Ave NE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15277- 1325 East Capitol St. SE, 1989 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15296- 1318 Independence Ave SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15304- Parry and Romani Associates Inc. Property, 233 Constitution Ave NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15309- Littlefield Property, 627 Massachusetts Ave NE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15310- Gill Property, 226 12th St. SE, 1988 - 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15314- Carlson Property, 1301 East Capitol St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15321- McCulloch Property, 300 11th St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15325- Lester Property, 337 6th St. SE, 1971, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15329- Pressler Property, 527 2nd St. NE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15334- KP Corp Property, #2 18th St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15342- 600 and 700 2nd St. NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15349- Folger Shakespeare Memorial Library Property, 305 East Capitol St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 27)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15355- Bannerman Property, 730 15th St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 28)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15357- Carlson Property, 1307 East Capitol St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 29)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15381- Anderson Property, 1332 Massachusetts Ave SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 30)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15387- 545 7th St. SE, 1985, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 31)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15386- Capitol Hill Day School Property, 214 South Caroline Ave SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 32)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15387- 545 7th St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 33)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15402- Cooper Property, 1367 North Carolina Ave NE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 34)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15412- D.C. Government Property, 651 10th St. NE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 35)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15415- Tekeste Property, 1250 C St. NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 36)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15433- Villa Ventures Property, 203 and 205 12th St. NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 37)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15439- Nelson Property, 440 New Jersey Ave SE, 1977; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 38)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15448- Sliwka Property, 628 and 630 Brown's Court SE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 39)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15449- J. Kyle Enterprises Inc. Property, 1340 G St. SE, 1990; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 40)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15542- Capitol Hill Hospital Property, 708 Massachusetts Ave NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 157, Folder 41)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15450- Mount Joy Baptist Church Property, 514 4th St. SE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15456- Madden Property, 728 F St. NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15469- Bubar Estate Property, 415 East Capitol St. SE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15476- Scheuer Property, 315 East Capitol St. SE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15480- Anderson Property, 1509 North Carolina Ave NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15491- Eubank and Bowers Property, 711 East Capitol St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15495- Fassler Property, 437 5th St. NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15505- Bobb Property, 1333 Constitution Ave NE, 1990 - 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15512- Weintraub Property, 409 4th St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15515- Depew Property, 509 5th St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15528- Berens and Borges Inc. Property, 701-719 Odd Numbers only 8th St. NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15529- 770 Limited Partnership Property, 770 M St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15535- Klein and DeFord Property, 206 Kentucky Ave SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15550- Benson and Anderson Property, 18 3rd St SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15556- Kloner Property, 629 East Capitol St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15557- C.W.C. Inc. Property, 1115 Pennsylvania Ave SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15561- Harbin Property, 500 9th St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15567- Winberg Property, 121 C St. SE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15569- Rome Baptist Church Property, 815 and 817 A St. NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15574- Taylor Property, 222 12th Place NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15574- American Association for Counseling and Development Property, 901 East Capitol St. SE, 1983, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15576- Long Property, 329 15th St. NE, 1991; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15579- 415 3rd St. NE, 416 and 424 4th St. NE, 1991 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15580- The American Committee on U.S. Soviet Relations Property, 109 11th St. SE, 1983; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 24)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15620- Lemon Property, 1704 C St. NE, 1991 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 25)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15657- Marsel Elliot Inc. Property, 1620 C St. SE, 1991 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 26)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15658- Mushtaha Property, 1233 MAssachusetts Ave SE, 1990 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 27)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15653- Box Property, 1712, 1714 and 1716 A St. SE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 28)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15659- Vogt Property, 815 C St. (Rear) NE, undated; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 29)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15672- East Capitol St. Association Property, 822 East Capitol St. NE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 30)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15688- Newsome Property, 613 14th St. NE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 31)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15694- Contrast Holding Co. Inc. Property, 1247 E St. NE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 32)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15695- Fuchs Property, 320 E St. NE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 33)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15710- Johnson Property, 1329 Constitution Ave NE, 1991 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 34)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15719- Rosenblith and Gardner Property, 246 11th St. SE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 158, Folder 35)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15736- Goldberg Property, 230 8th St. SE, 1992; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15737- Tucker Property, 160 12th St. SE, 1991 - 1992; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15779- Avatar Builders and Developers Inc. Property, 1525 A St. SE, 1992 - 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15781- Constitution Avenue General Partnership Property, 1334 Constitution Ave NE, 1992 - 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15786- Lovatelli Property, 238 9th St. SE, 1992 - 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15791- St. Mary Ame Zion Church Property, 1339 C St. NE, 1992 - 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15819- Wood Property, 530 13th St. SE, 1992 - 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15833- Glassman Property, 222 11th St. NE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15853- Bock Property, 646 5th St. NE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15866- McCall Property, 219 3rd St. NE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15870- Capitol Hill Holdings Inc. Property, 200 and 220 C St. SE, 1982, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15877- Sik and Kim Property, 700 F St. NE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15884- Burns Property, 1434 Independence Ave SE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15890- Branand Property, 412 South Capitol St. SE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15899- Thomas Property, 716 and 718 I St. SE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15900- Bowes Property, 700 North Carolina Ave SE, 1993; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15903- Morgan Property, 18 14th St. NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15915- Contex, Inc. Property, 18 7th St. NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15923- Bobb Property, 1333 Constitution Ave NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15928- DC Department of Housing and Community Development Property, 411-455 17th St. NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15931- Sinister Property, 606 E St. NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15961- Webb Property, 400 Constitution Ave NE, 1993 - 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15966- Potomac Investment Properties Inc. Property, 1015 Half St. SE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15968- Gates Property, 819 East Capitol St. SE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15972- Hoadley Proeprty, 706 3rd St. NE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15976- Utley Property, 156 11th St. NE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15978- 1115-1131 New Jersey Ave SE, 1994 - 1995; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15981- Rands Property, 709 11th St. NE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 28)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 15995- Donelson Property, 233 17th St NE, 1994; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 29)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16037- Yellen and Brocks Property, 810 E St. SE, 1996; Series 13 (Box 159, Folder 30)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16060- Neuman Property, 121 E St. SE, 1995 - 1996; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16062- Wye Property, 203 8th St. SE/725 Independence Ave SE, 1995; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16087- 1325 Independence Ave SE, 1995 - 1996; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16099- Byrd Property, 1251 Walter St. SE, 1995 - 1996; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16107- Norton Property, 10 9th St. SE, 1995 - 1996; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16108- African American Catholic Congregation Property, 609-611 Maryland Ave NE, 1993, 1995; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16120- Capitol Hill Day School Property, 214 South Carolina Ave SE, 1995 - 1996; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16125- Heu and Kim Property, 601 Massachusetts Ave NE, undated; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16131- Ellen Wilson Redevelopment Limited Liability Co., Various Properties, Series 13; 1995 ontainer id="aspace_e5819b9771edb33846bc8c0496270b06" label="Text [32882018204050]" type="Box">160 9
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16150- Gemmill Property, 215 10th St. SE, Series 13; 1995 ontainer id="aspace_35add9645a9dcb08655f83ca06a2c889" label="Text [32882018204050]" type="Box">160 10
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16171- Banneker Property, 730 15th St. SE, Series 13; 1995 ontainer id="aspace_5e30693675e45c9272c0c2300be7eba4" label="Text [32882018204050]" type="Box">160 11
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16211- 100 Maryland Ave NE, 1996 - 1997; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16247- Brylawski Property, 224 East Capitol St. NE, 1981 - 1998; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16250- Kaiser Investments Co. Property, 415 3rd St. NE, 416 and 424 4th St. NE, 1997; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16256- Church of the Reformation Property, 226 East Capitol St. SE, 1997; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16266- McCulloch Property, 300 11th St. SE, 1997; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16283- Graeter and Miller Property, 815 Rear C St. NE, 1992, 1997; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16321- Capitol Hill LLC Property, 719 D St. SE, 1996 - 1998; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16418- Sealander Property, 315 G St. SE, 1998 - 1999; Series 13 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16202- Marquette University Property, 502 East Capitol St. NE, 1996 - 1998; Series 13 (Box 161, Folder 1 (1/2))
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16202- Marquette University Property, 502 East Capitol St. NE, 1996 - 1998; Series 13 (Box 161, Folder 2 (2/2))
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16235- Marquette University Property, 502 East Capitol St NE, 1996 - 1998; Series 13 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 16351- Skirpa Property, 309 6th St. SE-517 Seward Square SE, 1997 - 1999; Series 13 (Box 161, Folder 4)